212articles.com 2010-12-23

# Privacy Policy

**General Information**

Using 212articles Website, its content, services and information, you will have to provide some personal information. 212articles takes extra care to protect your privacy. Our Privacy Policy will explain the way in which 212articles will collect, use, and disclose your personal information. 

**User Consent**

BY ACCESSING THE WEB SITE LOCATED AT THE URL [WWW.212ARTICLES.COM](http://www.212articles.com/), AND/OR BY ACCESSING ANY OTHER SITE PROVIDED BY 212articles YOU ARE PROVIDING YOUR CONSENT TO ALL THE INFORMATION COLLECTIING, INFORMATION USAGE, AND ALL OTHER PROCEDURES DESCRIBED IN THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY. 212articles has the right to change any part of this policy without notice at any time. If a new privacy policy will be posted at this location, the collection and usage of your private data by 212articles will be governed by that privacy policy. We strongly advise you to check our privacy policy regularly by visiting this page. Feel free to contact us at anytime if you have questions about our privacy policy.

**Collecting and Using the Information**

In order to sign up as an author or to register as a user and to access certain information or certain pages, you will be required to provide some personal information. This information will include your name, your e-mail address, your phone number and possibly other information. We require this information so we can contact you and provide more information about our services. We will also contact you for commercial and/or internal purposes like market research or to better understand the demographics of our visitors, potential customers or partners. We will share some of this information with some of our authorized partners or other third parties who act on our behalf, but we won’t provide or sell the personal information we gather on this Site to any outside marketers.

**Tracking our Users**

212articles uses some user tracking features in order to monitor the activities of every unique visitor.  We track our registered visitors as well as the anonymous ones. If you don’t register on our site or fill in your personal information on any forms, you will remain anonymous and we won’t discover your identity. But if you do register on 212articles, we will use our tracking features and we will be able to identify your future activities as well as your activities before the registration. We will identify the pages you visited on our site, the search engine you used to reached our reached our Site, etc.  We use these user tracking features in order to better understand our visitor’s needs and interests so we can improve our services and the experience of our users. This is designed to improve our marketing processes as well.

**212articles - Use of Cookies**

"Cookies" are small text files transferred by the Web Sites you visit to your computer while you are browsing that Web Site. Even if you don’t register on 212articles, after your first visit on our site there will be a cookie stored on your computer and you will be automatically identified when you use this site.  We use these cookies in order to enable our user tracking features and for other technical reasons. The cookies will also “autofill” certain information on the forms on site so you won’t have to do it manually. The Cookies cannot be used to discover a user’s identity. We only know the details you provide and we won’t discover additional information. Furthermore, if you would like not to receive any cookies, you can easily change your browser’s configuration and refuse the cookies. You can also delete the cookies that have already been transferred to your computer.

**Internet Protocol Addresses (IP) - Policy**

We will collect the IP address of any of our visitors .We will use your IP address in order to keep good administration of our site and our server as well as to gather information about the demographics of our users.  This is also designed to help us track our site’s users as described above.

**Use of Hyperlinks**

212articles contains hyperlinks that direct the user to other web sites. Our privacy policy applies only to 212articles and not to the sites you access by following a hyperlink from our site. 212articles is not responsible or liable in any way and nor are we in any control over those web sites and their content. Their collection and use of your personal information is subject to their own privacy policy and we strongly advise you to read the privacy policy before you take any actions on that site. In order to better protect the confidentiality of our users’ personal information, 212articles applies strict security measures due to the sensitivity of this information. However, the nature of the Internet technologies is such that not all security and privacy risks can be completely eliminated, and so, 212articles cannot provide absolute guarantees that your personal information won’t be disclosed. 212articles takes responsibility only for the above stated Privacy Policy.

**Our 3rd Party Based Advertising Policy**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on 212articles.com.  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.  
You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
